Guide to the Paul Ehrlich Papers SC0223
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Publications, Series 6
  - Article "Overcrowding and Us", 1968 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Article "Paying the Piper" 1967 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Article "Hunger, Population, and the Facts of Life", 1968 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Article "Population and Environment" 1967 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Article "Population, Food and Environment: is the Battle Lost?" 1967 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Article "The Population Crisis: Is our end of the boat sinking?", 1968 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Article by Johnson Montgomery for the Hastings Law Journal, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Biological and Reference Lists, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Articles from France (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Articles 1962-1968 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Articles, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Articles 1970, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Articles 1970, Folder 2 of 3 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Articles 1970, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Articles 1971, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Articles 1971, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Articles 1972, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Articles 1972, Folder 2 of 3 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Articles 1972, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Articles, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Articles, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Articles 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Articles (no date, est. 1970-1974) Folder 1 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Articles (no date, est. 1970-1974) Folder 2 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Articles on Crowding, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Articles in Saturday Review 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Article in Penthouse, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Articles 1965-1967 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Articles, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Articles, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Articles, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Articles, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Articles 1972-1974 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Articles not dated 1965-1974, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Articles not dated 1965-1974, Folder 2 of 3 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Articles not dated 1965-1974, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Book Review, The Population Bomb, 1968-1970, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Book Review, The Population Bomb, 1968-1970, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Book Review, The Silent Spring 1962 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - Hastings Law School Paper, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - Questionnaires on Population, Resources, Environment, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - Book Review, The End of Affluence 1974, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - Book Review, The End of Affluence 1974, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - Book, "Readings in Man, The Environment and Human Ecology" (pg. 235), 1973 (Box 27)
  - Book, "Project Survival" (pg. 65), 1971 (Box 27)
  - Book, "Tomorrow" (pg. 109), 1973 (Box 27)
  - Book, "Population Environment & People" (pg. 8), 1971 (Box 27)
  - Book, "Ecocide and Population" (pg. 28), 1972 (Box 27)
  - Book, "Growth of Population" (pg. 120), 1969 (Box 27)
  - Book, "Is the Bible Really the Word of God?" (pg. 125), 1969 (Box 27)
  - Book, "Prospect 2000" (pg. 194), 1979 (Box 27)
  - Book, "Ecocide" (pg. 21), 1971 (Box 27)
  - Book, "Environmental Solutions" (pg. 13), 1972 (Box 27)
  - Book, "Eco-Catastrophe" (pg. 1), 1970 (Box 27)
  - Book, "Rhetorical Considerations" (pg. 477), 1980 (Box 27)
  - Book, "Introductory Sociology" (pg. 78), 1981 (Box 27)
  - Books:
    - Grant, Lindsey. Elephants in the Volkswagen (Box 28)
    - Coomer, James C., ed. Quest for a Sustainable Society [2 cc] (Box 28)
    - Dryzek & Schlosberg, eds. Debating the Earth (Box 28)
    - Cohen & Lee, eds. Nuclear Weapons and the Future of Humanity (Box 28)
    - A Better Future for the Planet Earth, Vol. II [2 cc] (Box 28)
    - Leggett, Jeremy, ed. Global Warming; the Greenpeace report. (Box 28)
    - Earth Island Institute. The Second Biennial Conference on the Fate of the Earth; Peace on and with the Earth for all its Children. (Box 28)
    - Huddle, et. al. Island of Dreams; environmental crisis in Japan (Box 28)
    - Taylor, L. R., ed. The Optimum Population for Britain (Box 28)
    - Smith, Philip B., et. al., eds. The World at the Crossroads (Box 28)
    - Wolbarst, Anthony B., ed. Environment in Peril (Box 28)
    - Population: Opposing Viewpoints (Box 28)
    - Moore, John A. Science as a Way of Knowing – Human Ecology. American Society of Zoologists Annual Meeting December, 1984 (Box 28)
    - Menn, Julius J., ed. Progress and Perspectives for the 21st Century (Box 28)
    - Potter, Christopher S., et. al, eds. Perspectives on Biodiversity: Case Studies of Genetic Resource Conservation and Development. (Box 28)
    - The Population Bomb? Discussion on Demography (Box 28)
    - Ehrlich, Anne H., ed. Hidden Dangers (Box 28)
    - Population Law and Policy Conference: From Malthus to the Millennium, April 11-12, 1997 (Box 28)
  - Journals:
    - Revista de la Escuela Nacional de Inteligencia. Vol 1. Nu. 1 (Box 29)
    - Ambio; a journal of the human environment, June 2002 (Box 29)
    - American Zoologist. Vol. 25 No. 2, 1985 (Box 29)
    - Journal of Policy History. Vol. 12, No. 1, 2000 (Box 29)
    - Social Science Quarterly, Vol. 62, No. 1, March, 1981 (Box 29)
    - The Georgia Review. Summer 1991 [2 cc] (Box 29)
    - Population and Development Review, Vol. 19, No. 1, March 1993 (Box 29)
- Biographical Material, Series 7 (Box 5)
- News Clippings/Press Releases, Series 8
  - Press Releases, 1970–1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Press Clippings, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 2-7)
  - Clippings and booklets on Peace and the international food supply, 1960-1967 (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
  - Clippings and booklets on Butterflies, Jasper Ridge and Evolution Studies, 1963-1967 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - Newspaper articles on Ehrlich, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Resumes of Ehrlich and others (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Clippings (in Flemish) from the Ecolloquium at the University of Leuven, Belgium, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
  - News Clippings, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 4-6)
  - News Clippings, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 8-9)
  - News Clippings, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - News Clippings, 1974-75 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Audiovisual Material, Series 9
  - Photos of Ehrlich, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Jasper ridge Biological Preserve, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Head shots, Folder 1 of 2, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Head shots, Folder 2 of 2, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Photos in Office, Folder 1 of 2, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Photos in Office, Folder 2 of 2, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ehrich speaking at UCLA, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Interview with CBS or BBC, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Photos taken by Ilka Hartman, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Paul and Anne in France, French newpaper photo, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Photos taken by Steve Frieberg, Folder 1 of 2, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Photos taken by Steve Frieberg, Folder 2 of 2, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Interview on KOCE-TV, Huntington Beach, CA, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Anne and Paul, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Photos in Paul's Office, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 15-16)
  - "Tomorrows Children", Perennial Education Inc., 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - "Beyond Conception" 16mm film reel in metal canister, 2 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - "Mitosis in Endosperm" by Bajer and Mole-Bajer, Cracow, Poland (silent), 3 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - "Heredity and Adaptive Change" 16mm film reel in metal canister from Encyclopedia Britannica Films, 4 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - "Heredity and Adaptive Change" (duplicate), Encyclopedia Britannica Films, 5 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - "Population Ecology"16mm film reel in metal canister in a brown box from Encyclopedia Britannica Films, 6 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - "Bildung der Teilungsspindel …" (German), Institute fur den Wissenschaftlichen Film, Gottingen, 7 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - "Spermatogenese bei Pales ferriginea" (German), Institute fur den Wissenschaftlichen Film, Gottingen, 8 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 2)
  - Ehrlich speech at Australian Medical Conference, "Cyldon", 1971; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 2)
  - Ehrlich interview on KMOX radio, St. Louis, "Melody", 1980; 1 audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 2)
  - "The Population Crisis", 1 audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 2)
  - Dennis Meadows, Jay Forrester, MIT Labs, 1 audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 2)
  - Ehrlich speech on Pollution at Wilcox High School, Santa Clara, 1970; 1 videotape reel(s) (Box 2)
  - "Late Night Line Up" show discussion of population problem 1971 (Scotland)¼ inch audio tape reel in box marked "Zonatape", 0 (Box 2)
  - "Next Question" show on KPIX-TV San Francisco, 1968; 1 audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 2)
  - Ehrlich interview, KMOX radio, St. Louis, "DUB of 9pm AYS", 1980; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - No title, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - "Voluntary Sterilization and the Population Crisis", Association for Voluntary Sterilization, 1 phonograph record (33rpm) (Box 2)
  - "Paul Ehrlich, Reel 1, Programs 1-13", 1 audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 3)
  - "Paul Ehrlich, Reel 2, Programs 14-25", 1 audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 3)
  - "Paul Ehrlich, Reel 3, Programs 26-38", 1 audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 3)
  - "Paul Ehrlich, Reel 4, Programs 39-50", 1 audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 3)
  - Popular music, "Cal hi-fi", 1 audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 3)
  - Classical music, "Sony Professional Recording Tape", 1 audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 3)
  - "Direct News", 1 audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 3)
  - "The Tonight Show", 1974; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 4)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1985-131
  - Notes, 1970-1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Invitations Declined 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Invitations Declined 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, National Union of Townswomen's Guilds, London 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Invitations Declined 1981, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Invitations Declined 1981, Folder 2 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Invitations Declined 1981, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Notes, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, The Good Samaritan Hospital, San Jose 1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Nova Law Center, Fort Lauderdale, Florida, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, The Kenna Club, Santa Clara University, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, University of Nebraska-Lincoln, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, The Nature Conservancy, San Francisco, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Support the Water Reform Initiative, Stanford, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Man, Wildlife, and the Public Lands, Bellevue, Idaho, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Academy of Sciences, San Francisco, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, WGBH Boston, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Soviet Economic Scientific Institutions, Moscow, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Montshire Museum of Science, New Hampshire, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Students for Environmental Concerns, Champaign, Illinois, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Indiana Audubon Society, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Environmental Round Table, Marine County, California, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Rotary Club of San Mateo, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, FEAT Foundation, Flint, Michigan, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, Entomological Society of Canada, Guelph, Ontario, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, Golden Gate Audubon Society, Berkeley, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, Energy Exploration and Exploitation Institute, Edinburgh, Scotland, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, Stanford in Britain, Clivenden, England, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Invitations Declined, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, Plenum Publishing Corporation, New York, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, California State College, Bakersfield, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Environmental Defense Center, Santa Barbara, California, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Resource Policy Center, Dartmouth College, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Stanford Alumni Association, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Exxon Research Club, New Jersey, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Gilbert Masters, Stanford, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Marriage and Family Review, University of Delaware, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Michael Porter, Berkeley, California, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Hearing before the Subcommittee on Select Revenue Measures, US Congress, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Summary of the T-2000 Conference, San Diego, California, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Committee for Humane Legislation, Washington D.C, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, The American Naturalist Journal, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Outside Magazine, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Ecology Magazine, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Research Center for Ecology, Beijing, China, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, University of Colorado, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Bioscience Magazine, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, City College of San Francisco, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, American Society for Cybernetics, George Mason University, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Resume for Carrie Shaw, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Michigan State University, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Refusal letters, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Magic Inc., Stanford, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, The Four Corners, La Honda, California, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, Georges C. Panco, Paris, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, The Permanente Group, Hayward, California, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, Center for Ethics and Social Policy, Berkeley, California, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, Lane Community College, Eugene Oregon, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, Annual Review of Entomology, Palo Alto, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, Canadian National Collection, Quebec, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, Stockholm International Peace Research Institute, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, Dr. J. J. Head, Hampton, England, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, Richard R. Heath, San Francisco, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, UCLA Extension, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, Daniel D. Chiras, Engelwood, Colorado, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, University of Wisconsin-Eau Claire, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - National Science Foundation Grant 1972 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Hysteria against Environmentalists 1972, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Hysteria against Environmentalists 1972, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - War on Hunger Conference 1968 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Reaction to Papal Encyclical 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Posters:
    - Hiroshima Santa Cruz, 1985 (Box 2)
    - The Cold in the Dark" 1983 (large copy) (Box 2)
    - The Cold in the Dark" 1983 (small copy) (Box 2)
    - Zero Population Growth (no date) (2 copies) (Box 2)
    - Zero Population Growth, Mr. And Mrs. Lennon (no date) (Box 2)
    - Speech in Wellington, New Zeeland 1974 (Box 2)
  - Introduction speech by Donald Kennedy at the Conference on the Long-term Consequences of Nuclear War, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Summary paper from the Conference on the Long-term Consequences of Nuclear War, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Rough Draft of the Summary paper of the Conference on the Long-term Consequences of Nuclear War, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Review of the Summary paper from the Conference on the Long-term Consequences of Nuclear War, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence from Carl Sagan on the Summary paper from the Conference on the Long-term Consequences of Nuclear War, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Notes on the Conference on the Long-term Consequences of Nuclear War, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Framed Portrait of Paul Ehrlich (8" x 10") 1986 (est.) (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1994-007
  - Stanford Daily: Friday, April 1, 1983 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - 1982. Jan. 3-8. AAAS meetings--Endangered species Symposium (Box 1)
  - Jan 4-6, 1982 AAAS--Wash. DC (Box 1)
  - Jan 11, 1982: Raven Seminar (Box 1)
  - 1/30/82--Concord--Century Club (Box 1)
  - St. Louis: Feb 25, 1982 (Box 1)
  - AHE--St. Louis: Feb. 25, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Feb. 23, 1982--Rockford College, Ill. (Box 1)
  - Feb. 24, 1982--Marietta College, Ohio (Box 1)
  - 1982. March 24. Sydney, Australia. Birch lecture (Box 1)
  - Royal Viking--1982, Mar 26--May 8 (Box 1)
  - May 13, 1982--Sierra Club (P.A.) (Box 1)
  - June 2, '82--P.A., Sierra Club (Box 1)
  - June 14--16, '82 -- London (Cancel) (Box 1)
  - Sept. 82, World Bank, Wash. D.C. (Box 1)
  - Sept. 11-12, '82--Wash., D.C. (Zoo) (Box 1)
  - MAB #2 (Box 1)
  - Summer 1982--Soule-August Meetings: Inst. Transcultural Studies (Box 1)
  - October 13, '82- Milwaukee (Marquette) (Box 1)
  - October 12, 1982--Dillon, CO: Keystone (Box 1)
  - Oct. 15, '82--Detroit--Nat. Assn. Bio. Teachers (Box 1)
  - Oct. 17, '82--Chicago--Field Museum (Box 1)
  - Boston (Box 1)
  - Oct. 20, 1982. N.Y. City = Fate of the Earth (Box 1)
  - Oct. 21, '82--Hamilton, Ont.: Univ. Est. Ont. (Box 1)
  - October Trip (Box 1)
  - Oct. 26, 1982--Cal Acad. (Box 2)
  - Berkeley, Oct. 29, 1982 Euphydryas research (Box 2)
  - Nasser Nov 17 (Box 2)
  - Rotary Club 11/22/82 (Box 2)
  - Jan. 23--Feb. 5, 1983. BoraBora, MO (Box 2)
  - KPP England, November 20-23, 1983 (Box 2)
  - The Woodlands Forum, Fall 1984 (Box 2)
  - Travel Info. Misc. (Box 2)
  - DC Jan 25-26 (Box 2)
  - Gordon Conference, Ventura California: Jan 10-14, 1983 (Box 2)
  - Denver: Feb. 18 (Box 2)
  - Energy, Food, and You--Seattle Oct. 28 (Box 2)
  - Swarthmore: Spring, 1983 (Box 2)
  - Jefferson State Jr. College, Birmingham Alabama: February 16, 1983 (Box 2)
  - Vanderbilt University, Feb. 17 (Box 2)
  - 1983: Feb. 14-15. Univ. Texas (Box 2)
  - Riverside, U.C. Spring, 1983: Seminar (Box 2)
  - Earthweek SP (Box 2)
  - Great Valley Museum April 14, 1983 (Box 2)
  - No. Arizona University, Aug. 10-12 (Box 2)
  - Shoreline Community College: Seattle, Wash. April 1983 (Box 2)
  - Laurentian University, Ontario: October 20-22, '83 (Box 2)
  - Universidad Politecnica De Madrid (Box 2)
  - Spain (Box 2)
  - University of Utah, Salt Lake City: May (Box 2)
  - 1983. May 6-7. Kelly, Wyo.: Gr. Teton Science School (Box 2)
  - Sweden: Sept. (Box 2)
  - Greece/Margaris (Box 2)
  - Finland (Box 2)
  - France & England (Box 2)
  - Stanford Arms Control October 1983\ (Box 3)
  - Van Den Bosch Lecture (Box 3)
  - Lawrence, Kansas: 11/20/83 (Box 3)
  - Ottawa, Dec. 8: Radiation and its effects on life (Box 3)
  - UCSC Nov. 16 (Box 3)
  - Cambridge DBC (Box 3)
  - Nuclear Freeze Foundation 12/8/83 (Box 3)
  - ABC Nightline 12/30/83 (Box 3)
  - Austin, March 1984 (Never materialized) (Box 3)
  - Abraham Lincoln Brigade, Hayword, CA: Feb. 26, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Trinity University, San Antonio TX: March 14, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Flagstaff, April 2-3 (Box 3)
  - Western Maryland College, Westminster MD: March 16, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Africa, Jan. 84 (Box 3)
  - University of Texas, Dallas: March 15, 1984 (Box 3)
  - UC-Irvine/PSR: Feb. 15, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Carolina Symposium, UNC Chapel Hill: March 19, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Japan TV: April 26 (Box 3)
  - Cal Tech: May 23 (Box 3)
  - Northwestern: 5/8/84 (Box 3)
  - Princeton: May 7, 1984 (Box 3)
  - LA Psychiatric Assoc. (Box 3)
  - UCLA Seminar (Box 3)
  - Louis Alverez, Berkeley: 5/21 (Box 3)
  - Iowa City/PSR (Cancelled) (Box 3)
  - Santa Barbara Museum (Box 3)
  - LLNL Workshop: 6/11-12 (Box 3)
  - Harold Brun Society, SF: June 4 (Box 3)
  - AAAS--San Francisco: 6/10-16 (Box 3)
  - CAL State, Fresno: 10/8/84 or 10/22/84 (Box 3)
  - British Columbia, 10/19 (Box 3)
  - Conofoe (Box 3)
  - Commonwealth Club: Aug. 30, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Meeting Memo: June 1984 (Box 4)
  - George Mason University 9/18/84 (Box 4)
  - Fresno: Oct 24 (Box 4)
  - Scottsdale: April 4 (Box 4)
  - Michigan: May 7 (Box 4)
  - Stoneybrook: Dec 6 (Box 4)
  - Columbia Reunion: Oct. 27 (Box 4)
  - England: Nov. 84 (Box 4)
  - Univ. Maryland: Sept. 5 (Box 4)
  - Alaskans For World Peace: Juneau & Fairbanks, Alaska (Box 4)
  - National Lawyers Guild: Monterey, 9/23/84 (Box 4)
  - So. Bay Lawyers Guide: June 1-15 (Box 4)
  - Pompano Beach, Fl. Spring 1985 (Box 4)
  - Newport Beach, Ca.: Nov 15, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Fresno, 1985A: Pending (Box 4)
  - Brown--Pending (Box 4)
  - SACDF--Maddox Stanford: 12/1/84 (Box 4)
  - Phone Interview Houston: Nolan (Box 4)
  - Johns Hopkins 9/22 (Box 4)
  - U. Colorado--Boulder (Box 4)
  - Vermont (Box 4)
  - Cortland (Box 4)
  - U. of Oregon (Box 4)
  - KPEN: Call Sept. (Box 4)
  - Moravian College (Box 4)
  - SAAWOK: Denver, Dec., 27-28 (Box 4)
  - California State: Fullerton (Box 4)
  - New Forum: Oct. 18 (Box 4)
  - NAPA 10/10/84 (Box 4)
  - Grasslands (Box 4)
  - Bates College: March 85 (Box 4)
  - Palm Springs: March 1985 (Box 4)
  - South Carolina: March 19 (Box 4)
  - SLAC Colloquium: 84-85 (Box 4)
  - Arizona: May 1985 (Box 4)
  - Walnut, CA (Box 4)
  - Santa Cruz: May 14 (Box 4)
  - Montana (Box 4)
  - Dictionary (Box 5)
  - Simon & Schuster: Healthy Living in an Unhealthy World (Box 5)
  - (Foreword): The Condor Question, FOE--1981. (Box 5)
  - Endorsement: Nuclear Weapons Freeze 12/81 (Box 5)
  - Misc. Endorsements (Box 5)
  - Endorsement--Einstein Peace Prize Foundation: 1981 (Box 5)
  - Endorsement--Nader Book--'81 (Box 5)
  - (Review) Overshoot, by Catton. Amer. Scientist, 1981. (Box 5)
  - Blurb, W.J. Davis: The Seventh Day, 1/81 (Box 5)
  - Blurb, W. Murdoch, Poverty of Nations, 1/81 (Box 5)
  - The Book of Prediction, (People's Almanac), Wallechinsky, ed., 1980.-- (Box 5)
  - "Survivors envy the dead," PRE (Box 5)
  - Funk & Wagnalls New Encyclopedia 1983: "Butterflies & moths" (Box 5)
  - Untitled: Miscellaneous correspondence and papers (Box 5)
  - Jacket Blurb--UCS energy Study, eds. 1980 (Box 5)
  - Blurb for Steve Schneider, "Genesis Strategy," Plenum 1980-1 (Box 5)
  - Urban Environment Conference, Inc. Wash., D.C. endorsement, 1979 (Box 5)
  - Endorsement, Random House book on Yosemite, 1981 (Box 5)
  - La Force Vivant by Jean Dorst (Box 5)
  - Jacket blurb, AT HIGHEST RISK, by Christopher Norwood, 1979 (Box 5)
  - Ms. Magazine (PRE Statement) 1971 (Box 5)
  - Ministry of Ecology--statement 1/78 (Box 5)
  - Endorsement--Cerell, Anti-abortion initiative defeat. 1978 (Box 5)
  - Norman Myers, THE SINKING ARK, PRE endorsed 8/79 (Box 5)
  - AT HIGHEST RISK by Chris Norwood, McGraw Hill, 1979. Promo quote. (Box 5)
  - Biograffiti by John Ogden, blurb. 1980. (Box 5)
  - Michael Brown, Laying Waste: Love Canal & Poisining of America. 1980 (Box 5)
  - The Atlas of Planet Management, Pearson (Box 5)
  - Intro to Norman Myers Book (Box 5)
  - Peterson--Printers (Box 5)
  - Counterfeit Ark--Leaning (Box 5)
  - Genetics and the Extinction of Butterfly Populations (Box 5)
  - Chp. in Genetics & Conservation, Schonewald et al,. eds. (Box 5)
  - African Environmental Assn. Dora Obi Chizea, Pres. 1973-1974 (Box 5)
  - Foreward. GROUND FOR CONCERN: Australia's Uranium and Human Survival. Mary Elliot, ed. Penguin 1977. (Box 5)
  - Book on military, economic, environmental issues by John Weldon 4/78 (Box 5)
  - Int'l Conference on Conservation Biology, ed. Bruce Wilcox 1979 (Box 5)
  - Conservation Symposium Paper (For Publication in book by Sinauer Assoc. (Box 5)
  - Conservation Symposium, San Diego 1978 (Box 5)
  - Blurb for book by W. Jack davis, 1979 (Box 5)